(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
兎田ぺこら 3周年記念
SUMMER Party
Usada Pekora 3rd Anniversary
Go!
キスをあげるよ
I'll give you a kiss
今気付いた想い
The feelings I just realized
どんな言葉でも足りないから
Because no words are enough
1, 2, 3, 4!
初恋サイダー
First Love Cider
甘えすぎてるかな?
Am I being too spoiled?
友達の時間が長かったせいで
Because we were just friends for so long
あなたの癖や性格だって
Even your habits and personality
他の子より知ってるの
I know them better than any other girl
あぁ いじっぱりで
Ah, I think of you,
恥ずかしがり屋な あなたを想う
so stubborn and shy
待ってられないの
I can't wait any longer
キスをあげるよ
I'll give you a kiss
今更好きなんて
Saying "I love you" now
言葉より効き目あるでしょ
Would be more effective than words, right?
あなたにだけは
I'll tell only you
そっと教えてあげる
quietly
胸の奥
Deep in my heart
小さな蕾のぬくもり
The warmth of a tiny bud
時々甘えてみたり
Sometimes I try being spoiled
拗ねてみたり そんな作戦らしくない
Or try sulking, that strategy isn't like me
大体乙女って勝手なの
Mostly, girls are selfish
この恋だけは負けられない
I can't lose this love
あぁ 鈍感な
Ah, I want to make
あなたのハート振り向かせたいから
your dense heart turn my way
勝負かけるの
So I'm making my move
キスをあげるよ
I'll give you a kiss
今更好きなんて
Saying "I love you" now
言葉より効き目あるでしょ
Would be more effective than words, right?
あなたにだけは...
I'll tell only you...
いいでしょ 聞こえちゃう tonight
Is it okay? You'll hear it tonight
早くなるドキドキ
My heart starts beating faster
初恋はサイダーみたいに
First love is like cider
弾ける
Sparkling
友達同士 そんな境界線
Just friends, that's the current line
今すぐに飛び越えたいの
I want to jump over it right now
キスをあげるよ
I'll give you a kiss
今さら好きなんて
Saying 'I love you' now
言葉より 効き目あるでしょ
Is more effective than words, right?
あなたにだけは そっと教えてあげる
I'll tell only you, quietly
胸の奥 小さい 翼 の はばたく
Deep in my heart, the sound of small wings
音を...
flapping...
信じて
Believe in it
どっちが好きなのよ
Which one do you like?
いいわけバニー
Excuse Bunny
なんとかなんないかな？
Can't we do something about this?
ラビラビ 隣のあいつが邪魔だなぁ
Labi-labi, that guy next to me is in the way
よくないそんなこと ダメダメ
That's not good, no-no
selfish 絶対 永遠とは違うな
selfish, absolutely, it's not eternity
なんたって競争
After all, competition
苦手だそういうの
I'm bad at that kind of thing
何度も寂しい 気むずかし
Many times lonely, being difficult
練習したっけ？ ペコパレット好きでしょ
Did I practice? You like Peko Palette, right?
あの子に負けない けどだってジェラシー
I won't lose to that girl, but because of jealousy
欲張り目 横取りか してみます！ おー！
Greedy eyes, taking it away? I'll try it! Oh!
言わなきゃって分かってる
I know I have to say it
あーでもない こーでもない 夢にしましょう
Not this, not that, let's make it a dream
つらぬけ my my my...
Go through my my my...
聞きたくない いいわけバニー
I don't want to hear it, Excuse Bunny
地団駄の優柔不断だんだん
Stomping feet, indecisiveness gradually
バニバニ ダリダリ 待ちぼうけの話
Bunny-bunny, dally-dally, the story of being stood up
どっち どっちが好きなのよ
Which, which one do you like?
ダメダメ ダメダメ
No-no, no-no
逃げ出したいのは私の本音でしょ
Wanting to run away is my true feeling
通しません 反対方向
I won't let you through, opposite direction
Wanted! いいわけバニー
Wanted! Excuse Bunny
態度とか 言い回しとか
Your attitude, your phrasing
興味がねーから ちょー苦手
I'm not interested, I'm super bad at it
人込み 君探す はり込み
Stakeout in the crowd to find you
届け強気味
Deliver with high intensity
嫉妬だし 並ぶたび 微笑み
It's jealousy, smiling every time we're together
散々エイチの トラストチャンス はい、もっと！
Endless H's trust chance, yes, more!
前身あるのみ トラブルでエンドに
Only moving forward, ending in trouble
閃動だ あんたたち やっちゃいましょ！
It's a flash, everyone, let's do this!
疲れちゃった ひと休み
I'm tired, let's take a break
なんとかね やってよね 明日の私
Somehow, handle it, tomorrow's me
任せろ my my my...
Leave it to me my my my...
決められない いいわけバニー
I can't decide, Excuse Bunny
有耶無耶演出は 功徳 争争争
Vague production is merit, struggle struggle
メニメニ モニモニ 待ちぼうけの話
Many-many, moni-moni, the story of being kept waiting
ほら ほら 私はもう
Look, look, I'm already
ダメダメ ダメダメ
No-no, no-no
遊びじゃないです それなんて
This is not a game, that is
恋ってない 私一途な本音でしょ
Not love, it's my single-minded true feeling
参りません 逃がさない
I won't give in, I won't let you escape
どこへだって 行けばいい
You can go anywhere you want
言い訳ない 容赦しない 冗談じゃない
No excuses, no mercy, no joking around
ぶつけろ my my my...
Strike it my my my...
聞きたくない いいわけバニー
I don't want to hear it, Excuse Bunny
地団駄の優柔不断だんだん
Stomping feet, indecisiveness gradually
バニバニ ダリダリ 待ちぼうけの話
Bunny-bunny, dally-dally, the story of being stood up
どっち どっちが好きなのよ
Which, which one do you like?
ダメダメ ダメダメ
No-no, no-no
逃げ出したいけど 私しかないでしょ
I want to run away, but it's only me, right?
通しません 反対方向
I won't let you through, opposite direction
Wanted! いいわけバニー
Wanted! Excuse Bunny
そんなんで いいわけバニー
Like that, Excuse Bunny
はい！ってなわけで
Yes! And so
1曲目は初恋サイダー
the first song was Hatsukoi Cider
そして2曲目はいいわけバニー...
and the second song was Iiwake Bunny...
ハニードーペコかー？
Is everyone having a good time?
楽しんでくれているペコかー？
Are you guys enjoying yourselves?
この後もコラボだったり、
There will be collaborations and
色々メドレーだったりもあるペコだから、
various medleys coming up...
ぺこーらの３周年ライブ、楽しみにしててねー！
So please look forward to Pekora's 3rd anniversary live!
じゃあ早速行ってみよう！バイバイ！
Well then, let's get started! Bye-bye!
君がいた夏は 遠い夢の中
The summer you were here is in a distant dream
空に消えてった 打ち上げ花火
Skyward, they vanished, the launched fireworks
夏祭り / 作詞・作曲 破矢ジンタ
Summer Festival / Lyrics & Composition: Haya Jinta
君の髪の香り はじけた 浴衣姿がまぶしすぎて
The scent of your hair, your yukata-clad figure was so dazzling
お祭りの夜は 胸が騒いだよ
On the night of the festival, my heart was all a-flutter
はぐれそうな人混みの中 離れないで 出しかけた手を
In the crowd where we might get separated, "don't leave me," I almost reached out my hand
ポケットに入れて 握りしめていた
I put it in my pocket and clenched it tight
君がいた夏は 遠い夢の中
The summer you were here is in a distant dream
空に消えてった 打ち上げ花火
Skyward, they vanished, the launched fireworks
BLUE BIRD / 作詞 浜崎あゆみ 作曲 D・A・I
BLUE BIRD / Lyrics: Hamasaki Ayumi, Composition: D・A・I
君はそっと見守ってた この背の翼
You were quietly watching over the wings on this back
飛び立つ季節を待って
Waiting for the season to take flight
青い空を共に行こうよ 白い砂浜を見下ろしながら
Let's go together across the blue sky, looking down at the white sandy beach
難しい話はいらない 君が笑ってくれればいい
No need for difficult talk, as long as you smile for me
青い空を共に行こうよ どこへたどり着くんだとしても
Let's go together across the blue sky, no matter where we end up
もしも傷を負ったその時は 僕の翼を君にあげる
If you ever get hurt, I'll give you my wings
そう言って君は少し泣いた
Saying that, you cried a little
こらえきれずに僕も泣いた
Unable to hold it back, I cried too
夏空グラフィティ / 作詞・作曲 水野良樹
Natsuzora Graffiti / Lyrics & Composition: Mizuno Yoshiki
世界で一番大好きなあなたが あたしの 一番大切な人だよ
You, whom I love most in the world, are my most precious person
その手をどんな時も信じているのは あたし一人だけだよ
I'm the only one who believes in that hand, no matter when
まぶしい太陽のきらめきの中で とびきり熱いまま恋をしたいよ
In the dazzling sparkle of the sun, I want to stay hot and in love
この手をいつまでも離しちゃいけないのは あなた一人だけだよ
You're the only one who should never let go of this hand
抱きしめていて
Keep holding me tight
め組のひと / 作詞 麻生圭二 作曲 井上大輔
Megumi no Hito / Lyrics: Aso Keiji, Composition: Inoue Daisuke
いなせだね 夏を連れてきた女（ひと）
You're so dashing, the woman who brought the summer
渚まで 噂走るよ めっ！
Rumors travel all the way to the beach! Me!
涼しげな 目もと流し目 eye eye eye
Cool eyes with a sidelong glance, eye eye eye
粋なこと 起こりそうだぜ めっ！
Something stylish is about to happen! Me!
妖しい 彗星（すいせい）で
With a mysterious comet
恵みの女（ひと）だね
You're the woman of grace
お前の ニュースで ビーチは 突然 パニック
With your news, the beach is suddenly in a panic
Baby, Baby, be-my-girl / 夢中なのさ be-my-girl
Baby, Baby, be-my-girl / I'm crazy about you, be-my-girl
浮気な微笑みに 俺たち Qumosabe-lo
At your fickle smile, we're Qumosabe-lo
男たちの 心 奪うたびに お前
Every time you steal the hearts of men
綺麗になってく めっ！
You become even more beautiful! Me!
夏の罪は 素敵すぎる
The sins of summer are just too wonderful
いなせだね 夏を連れてきた女（ひと）
You're so dashing, the woman who brought the summer
渚まで 噂走るよ めっ！
Rumors travel all the way to the beach! Me!
涼しげな 目もと流し目 eye eye eye
Cool eyes with a sidelong glance, eye eye eye
粋なこと 起こりそうだぜ めっ！
Something stylish is about to happen! Me!
Let's go Fever Time!
ラブリー☆えんじぇる!! / 作詞：しらたまぷりん 作曲：どれちゅ
Lovely Angel!! / Lyrics: Shiratama Purin Composition: Dorechu
Let's go Fever Time! / Ahah! Lovely Angel Chu Chu Chu!
Wow! Avenue Paradise! / Chu Chu Chu!
春風のトキメキに 恋の嵐を届けます
To the heart-throbs of the spring breeze, I'll deliver a storm of love
狙った獲物（サカナ）は 逃がすわけないし
There's no way I'll let my target get away
淡い光 包み込むよ 恋の矢 放ちます
Enveloped in a faint light, I'll release the arrows of love
どこまでも追いかけろ！ 護衛（ガード）はいりません
Chase me to the ends of the earth! No guard needed
天使がその 優しい瞳を まばたきする前に
Before the angel can blink her gentle eyes
全部まとめて 頂いちゃうからね イェイ！
I'm going to take it all together! Yay!
エンジェル・モードで わくわく
Excited in Angel Mode
君のハートを 盗めるのかな
I wonder if I can steal your heart?
抱きしめられたら はいはい！ このまま 奪われちゃうよ
If I'm hugged—yes, yes!—I'll be snatched away just like this
エンジェル・アローで ドキドキ
Heart pounding from the Angel Arrow
夢中にさせてね この笑顔
Make me crazy about that smile
君を見上げたら はいはい！ 眩しすぎて やっぱり好きでした
Looking up at you—yes, yes!—you're so dazzling, I really did love you
チュッ チュッ チュッ イェイ！
Chu Chu Chu Yay!
想いは晴れた空 君に届いたらいいのに
My feelings are like a clear sky; if only they would reach you
意地悪な神様 お願い この恋叶えて
Mean god, please make this love come true
空にきらり 青い空に 雲ひとつなくて Go!
Sparkling in the sky, in the blue sky, not a single cloud, Go!
晴れやかな気分 止まることなく 運命（さだめ）を待ちます
My sunny mood won't stop as I wait for destiny
いい加減な 恋の魔法より 奪います この手で
Better than some half-baked love magic, I'll take it with my own hands
君の心 鷲掴み イェイ！
Grabbing your heart! Yay!
エンジェル・モードで わくわく
Excited in Angel Mode
いつまでたっても 振り向かない
No matter how much time passes, you won't look back
瞳を閉じても はいはい！ 背伸びするなら手を繋ぐ
Even if I close my eyes—yes, yes!—if you're standing on tiptoe, hold my hand
エンジェル・アプローチで ドキドキ
Heart pounding from the Angel Approach
優しくそっと 抱き寄せてみて
Try gently pulling me close
鏡に映った はいはい！ 唇はずっと 君だけのもの
Reflected in the mirror—yes, yes!—my lips belong to you alone
Let's go Fever Time! / Yay! / Ahah! Lovely Angel
Chu Chu Chu! / Wow! Avenue Paradise! / Chu Chu Chu!
天使がその 優しい瞳を まばたきする前に
Before the angel can blink her gentle eyes
全部まとめて 頂いちゃうからね イェイ！
I'm going to take it all together! Yay!
エンジェル・モードで わくわく
Excited in Angel Mode
君のハートを 盗めるのかな
I wonder if I can steal your heart?
抱きしめられたら はいはい！ このまま 奪われちゃうよ
If I'm hugged—yes, yes!—I'll be snatched away just like this
エンジェル・アローで ドキドキ
Heart pounding from the Angel Arrow
夢中にさせてね この笑顔
Make me crazy about that smile
君を見上げたら はいはい！ 眩しすぎて やっぱり好きでした
Looking up at you—yes, yes!—you're so dazzling, I really did love you
チュッ チュッ チュッ イェイ！
Chu Chu Chu Yay!
ラブリー！ はいはい！
Lovely! Yes, yes!
あまにゅ！　Oh Happy! / チュン　チュン　チュン　ピュン　ピュン　ピュン
Amaniu! Oh Happy! / Chirp chirp chirp, zoom zoom zoom
あまにゅ！　Oh Lucky! / チュン　チュン　チュン　EVERY DAY
Amaniu! Oh Lucky! / Chirp chirp chirp, EVERY DAY
あまにゅ！　Oh Happy! / チュン　チュン　チュン　EVERY NIGHT
Amaniu! Oh Happy! / Chirp chirp chirp, EVERY NIGHT
Wow! La la la... / チュン　チュン　チュン　ピュン　ピュン　ピュン
Wow! La la la... / Chirp chirp chirp, zoom zoom zoom
ピュン　ピュン　ピュン　レッツゴー！　ハイッ！
Zoom zoom zoom, let's go! Hey!
姫が来てやったのらー！ / ありがとぺこー！
Hime is here for you, nanora! / Thank you, peko!
ぺこぺこ先輩三周年おめでとうぺこなのら！ / ルーナたーん！
Happy 3rd anniversary, Peko-Peko senpai-nanora! / Luna-tan!
会いに来たのら！じゃあ、またねー！ / ええっ！？
I came to see you! Well, see ya! / Ehh?!
待って！早すぎぺこ！ / な、なになに？
Wait! That was too fast, peko! / Wha- what is it?
寂しいぺこじゃん！1年に1度しか会えないコンビぺこらなんなのらね！
I was lonely, peko! We're a duo that only meets once a year, Peko-Luna-nanora!
ああ、そうだったのらね。1年ぶりなのらね。
Ah, that's right nanora. It's been a year, hasn't it nanora?
そうぺこなのらね！ちょっと、あまりにもさっぱりしすぎてびっくりしちゃったぺこ！
That's right, peko-nanora! I was surprised because you were way too detached about it, peko!
え、嫌われてるワンチャンあるぺこ？
Wait, is there a chance you hate me, peko?
そんなことないのらよ。ま、また来年！
That's not it, nanora. Well, see you next year!
ああー！ちょっとー！ルーナたーん！
Aaaah! Wait! Luna-tan!
いっせーのーで　君とだけ
Ready, set, go! Only with you
ハイタッチ☆メモリー / 作詞：ワタナベハジメ　作曲：高尾奏之介
High Touch Memory / Lyrics: Watanabe Hajime  Composition: Takao Sonosuke
もう少し眠りたいけど
I want to sleep a little longer, but...
もったいないよ　今日はサンデー
It's a waste, today is Sunday
楽しいこと　やりたいこと
Fun things, things I want to do
With us　始めようよ
With us, let's get started
めぐりめぐる　君と
Spinning and spinning with you
次のステージへ
To the next stage
声を合わせ　扉開けて
Harmonize our voices, open the door
駆け出せ　迷わずに
Run out without hesitation
転んでも　かっこ悪くても　いいじゃない
It's okay if you fall or look uncool
Stand up　イメージもっと　重ねてゆく
Stand up, let the images overlap more
その先に
Beyond that...
いっせーのーで　君とだけ
Ready, set, go! Only with you
ハイタッチして　手叩いて
Give me a high touch, clap your hands
奏でる　メロディを
The melody we play...
合図に走り出せば　君となら　怖くない
If it's the signal to start running, I'm not afraid with you
ハイタッチして　手叩いて
Give me a high touch, clap your hands
重ねる　そのメモリーは
The memories we pile up...
明日へのエネルギー
Are the energy for tomorrow
最高よ　もっと先へ
It's the best! Further ahead
君となら　半端じゃない
It's no joke if I'm with you
あの日見た夢の続き
The continuation of the dream I saw that day
追いつく　その日まで
Until the day I catch up to it
涙なんて　振り切るくらい
To the point of shaking off the tears
もっと　スピードアップ
Speed up even more
どんな未来に　なっても
No matter what the future holds
後悔しないよ
I won't regret it
自分自身　選んだ道
The path I chose myself
踏み出せ　迷わずに
Step forward without hesitation
落ち込んで　進めなくなった時は
When you're depressed and can't move forward
Wake up　思い返す　夢見た　この時を
Wake up, remember this moment you dreamed of
Wow wow
手と手で　奏でる
With hand in hand, playing a tune...
映える　きらめく　夢を　君とだけ
It shines and sparkles, a dream only with you
ハイタッチして　その旅に
Give me a high touch, on that journey...
繋がってゆく　心
Our hearts will be connected
一人じゃないことを　気づかせてくれたよね
You made me realize that I'm not alone
ハイタッチして　手叩いて
Give me a high touch, clap your hands
奏でる　そのメロディーが
The melody we play...
世界に届くまで
Until it reaches the world
この夢は続いてく
This dream will continue
君となら　半端じゃない
It's no joke if I'm with you
一人で歩けない日は
On days when you can't walk alone
おんぶしてあげる　君を
I'll give you a piggyback ride
空見て　そっちの方が
Look at the sky, that way...
強く地面　踏み込める
You can step on the ground even harder
めぐりめぐる　日々を
Spinning and spinning, through the days
たどり夢見た　ステージへ
To the stage I've struggled to dream of
届くその日を　見つめて
Gazing at the day it reaches...
起こそう　君とだけ
Let's make it happen, only with you
手と手を鳴らすたび
Every time we clap our hands together...
小さなビッグバン
A small big bang
無限の　その力を
Receive that infinite power...
受けて進め
And move forward
ハイタッチして　手叩いて
Give me a high touch, clap your hands
奏でる　メロディを
The melody we play...
合図に走り出せば　君となら　怖くない
If it's the signal to start running, I'm not afraid with you
ハイタッチして　手叩いて
Give me a high touch, clap your hands
重ねる　そのメモリーは
The memories we pile up...
明日へのエネルギー
Are the energy for tomorrow
最高よ　もっと先へ
It's the best! Further ahead
君となら　半端じゃない
It's no joke if I'm with you
コココココココ　ミツカラナイデ
パパイヤ マンゴー ココナッツ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co, don't find me
Papaya, mango, coconut
カキ氷 イチゴ味 メロンを出したらマッタッターイ！
Shaved ice, strawberry flavor
If I bring out the melon, it's time to wait!
チョチョチョイ チョイチョイ チョッチェ
チャチャチャチャチャチャチャーン
Cho-cho-choi choi-choi chocche
Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-n
ココナッツ Yeah!
Coconut Yeah!
カチカチに燃えているお兄様
バシュワ〜ココナッツ ベイベー
Big brother, burning bright
Bashuwa~ Coconut baby
待ちわびた季節の様様様様
バシュワ〜ココナッツ ベイベー
The long-awaited season's appearance
Bashuwa~ Coconut baby
甘いヒゲ 買っちゃった ビキニ
Sweet beard, I bought a bikini
すごく照れるけど 負けらんない
I'm so shy, but I won't lose
日焼け止めココナッツフレーバー
バシュワ〜ココナッツ ベイベー
Sunscreen, coconut flavor
Bashuwa~ Coconut baby
紫外線とココナッツレーザー
バシュワ〜ココナッツ ベイベー
UV rays and coconut laser
Bashuwa~ Coconut baby
ドキュン！ バキュン！ 君の視線
Dokyun! Bakyun! Your gaze
心臓 大爆発
My heart's big explosion
サシスセソ ココナッツ ベイベー
タチツテト ココナッツ ベイベー
Sa-shi-su-se-so, coconut baby
Ta-chi-tsu-te-to, coconut baby
カキクケコ ココナッツ ベイベー
サ〜サ〜サマ〜タイ Yeah!
Ka-ki-ku-ke-ko, coconut baby
Su-su-summertime Yeah!
コココココココ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co
ココココココココココココココココココナッツ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-coconut
コココナッツ
Co-coconut
カキ氷 メロン味 ベロを出したらゾンビダーイ！
Shaved ice, melon flavor
If I stick out my tongue, it's a zombie die!
アイウエオ ココナッツ ベイベー
チャチャチャチャチャチャチャーン
A-i-u-e-o, coconut baby
Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-n
ムシムシウンザリね 熱帯夜
バシュワ〜ココナッツ ベイベー
Fed up with the humid tropical nights
Bashuwa~ Coconut baby
ココナッツジュースのミタイナ
バシュワ〜ココナッツ ベイベー
I want to drink coconut juice
Bashuwa~ Coconut baby
長い夜で 短いサマタイ
Long nights and short summertime
ハチャメチャもん勝ち
サシスセソ ココナッツ ベイベー
The chaotic one wins
Sa-shi-su-se-so, coconut baby
タチツテト ココナッツ ベイベー
カキクケコ ココナッツ ベイベー
Ta-chi-tsu-te-to, coconut baby
Ka-ki-ku-ke-ko, coconut baby
サ〜サ〜サマ〜タイ Yeah!
Su-su-summertime Yeah!
コココココココ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co
ココココココココココココココココココナッツ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-coconut
コココナッツ
Co-coconut
オリアー！　シュシュシュバニー！
Oriaa! Shu-shu-shu bunny!
指輪〜！　指輪〜！
Rings! Rings!
ココココココココココココココココココ
アチアチのサマー　コップリハマッ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co
Hot hot summer, completely hooked
熱血アタック　バキュン！　バキュン！
様様様様　サシスセソ ココナッツ ベイベー
Hot-blooded attack, bakyun! bakyun! appearance
Sa-shi-su-se-so, coconut baby
タチツテト ココナッツ ベイベー
カキクケコ ココナッツ ベイベー　サ〜サ〜サマ〜タイ Yeah!
Ta-chi-tsu-te-to, coconut baby
Ka-ki-ku-ke-ko, coconut baby, su-su-summertime Yeah!
コココココココ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co
ココココココココココココココココココナッツ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-co-coconut
コココココココ　ミツカラナイデ
パパイヤ マンゴー ココナッツ
Co-co-co-co-co-co-co, don't find me
Papaya, mango, coconut
二人ともありがとうぺこー！
Thank you both, peko!
ぺこぺこ！ わーい！
Peko peko! Yay!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
三周年おめでとー！ ありがとうー！
Happy 3rd anniversary! Thank you!
笑顔出しちゃった。
I gave a big smile.
じゃあ、ちょっと、スクショ撮ってもらうよ。
Well, let's have them take some screenshots.
あ、いいねぺこ。DNPだもんね、こういうの。
Oh, that's good, peko. This is a DNP, right?
あ、ダブピだ。
Oh, it's a double peace.
ダブピーだ。ダブピーだ、可愛い。
Double peace. Double peace, so cute.
本当にダブピー、可愛かった。
The double peace was really cute.
おめでとう。
Congratulations.
あ、この次、あ、この次、あと、
また三人で一曲歌うぺこ。
Oh, next... Oh, next, we three are
going to sing one more song together, peko.
あ、ごめんぺこ、そろそろちょっとあの...
Ah, sorry peko, it's about time to...
え、何？
Eh, what?
次の曲、次の曲。
The next song, the next song.
いこういこう！
Let's go, let's go!
やだぺこ！ やだぺこ！
No way, peko! No way, peko!
ふざけんなぺこ！
Stop messing around, peko!
うさぎ、遅いぺこ！
Rabbits are slow, peko!
（笑い声）
(Laughter)
次の曲に行くぺこー！
Let's go to the next song, peko!
メンタルチェンソー
Mental Chainsaw
ハイ、末期さし　どん詰まり参事
Hey, terminal stage, a dead-end disaster.
くだらない脳細胞暗示
Trifling brain cell suggestion.
散々でバンジー
Bungee-jumping through terrible times.
追い詰まる心地　メンタルパンチ
Feeling backed into a corner, mental punch.
アハン　アハン
Ahan, ahan.
止まんない拍子
An unstoppable rhythm.
ハイ、末期症状　ハッピーの象徴
Hey, terminal symptoms, the symbol of happiness.
くだらない脳かき乱れ炎上
Trifling brain getting disturbed and bursting into flames.
仏様も万障
Even the Buddha faces all obstacles.
アン・ドゥ・トロワでシャン　モーメンタル故障
One, two, three and 'shan', momentary failure.
アハン　アハン
Ahan, ahan.
ふざけてんな
You're kidding me.
ダッダッダッダッ　首閉まって
Da-da-da-da, my neck is tightening.
ダッダッダッダッ　息づまりな
Da-da-da-da, I'm suffocating.
ダッダッダッダッ　夢見たって
Da-da-da-da, even if I dream.
どう転がっても平凡です
No matter how things go, it's just ordinary.
居たたまれないわ
I can't stand it.
ウザったい消えたい　もうイヤイヤイヤっての
So annoying, I want to disappear, I say no, no, no...
ウザったい消えたい　もうイヤイヤイヤっての「アーッ！」
So annoying, I want to disappear, I say no, no, no, "Aah!"
ダッダッダッダッ　吐き捨てんだ
Da-da-da-da, spit it out.
ダッダッダッダッ　笑えもっと
Da-da-da-da, laugh more.
ダッダッダッダッ　奈落情緒
Da-da-da-da, hellish emotions.
ダッダッダッダッ　DOWN！
Da-da-da-da, DOWN!
は？
Huh?
ハイ、末期でしょ　予備軍炎上
Hey, it's terminal, isn't it? The reserve forces are in flames.
くだらないの吸い込み御返上
Sucking in the trifling stuff and returning it.
不様は反証
Unseemliness is disproof.
はっ、もう丸腰　初心もなし
Hey, I'm unarmed now, no one else is here.
アハン　アハン
Ahan, ahan.
つまんないんだ
It's boring.
ダッダッダッダッ　突き切って
Da-da-da-da, break through.
ダッダッダッダッ　生きづらいの
Da-da-da-da, it's hard to live.
ダッダッダッダッ　明日もずっと
Da-da-da-da, tomorrow and forever.
どう頑張っても惨死です
No matter how hard I try, it's a tragic death.
アイ・モット・モット・モット・モット・熱唱
I, more, more, more, more, singing passionately.
アン・モット・モット・モット・モット・干渉
An, more, more, more, more, interference.
アイ・モット・モット・モット・モット・劣性
I, more, more, more, more, recessive.
アン・モット・モット・モット・モット・扇騒
An, more, more, more, more, chainsaw.
どう足掻いても酷いです
No matter how much I struggle, it's terrible.
居たたまれない　いたたたたたたまれない
I can't stand it, I can't-can't-can't-can't stand it.
ダッダッダッダッ　立ち上がって
Da-da-da-da, stand up.
ダッダッダッダッ　笑えいっそ
Da-da-da-da, just laugh.
ダッダッダッダッ　奈落情緒
Da-da-da-da, hellish emotions.
ダッダッダッダッ　DOWN！
Da-da-da-da, DOWN!
はい。
Yes.
ほ。
Huh.
ラプちゃん、来てくれてありがてぺこー！
Lap-chan, thanks for coming, peko!
来たぞー！
I'm here!
なんか軽くね？
Aren't you a bit too casual?
ぺこらさん、来たよ。
Pekora-san, I came.
ね、今日なんの日かわかってる？
Hey, do you know what day it is today?
あ！
Ah!
おめ...
Happ...
おめでとう言いに来たんだよ！ 3周年おめでとうございますって言うべきだよね、ぺこなの。
I came to say congratulations! I should say "Congratulations on your 3rd anniversary", right, peko.
呼んでくれてあざーっす。
Thanks for inviting me.
軽すぎなんだが、この人。何ニコニコしてんの。
This person is way too casual. What are you smiling about?
いや、めっちゃおめでたいっす。
No, it's really worth celebrating.
初めてのさ、コラボ、3Dコラボだったんだが、写真撮っていい？
It was our first 3D collab, can we take a photo?
あー、いいよ、しょうがない。
Ah, okay, I guess.
じゃあみんな、撮ってぺこなー！
Okay everyone, take a picture, peko!
あーかわいい。えっ、ちっちゃくてかわいいぺこだね！
Ah, cute. Wow, you're small and cute, peko!
ちっちゃい言うな、ちっちゃい言うな。
Don't say I'm small, don't say I'm small.
あー、かわいい、かわいい、かわいい。
Ah, cute, cute, cute.
特別ですよ、この写真。クソガキみたいでかわいい。
This photo is special. You're cute like a brat.
クソガキ言うな！
Don't call me a brat!
撮れました、お写真。
We got the photo.
やばい、そろそろお時間みたいぺこで。
Oh no, looks like it's almost time, peko.
はよ。
Quick.
急いで！早く行くよ！
Hurry! Let's go quickly!
えっ、どこ、どこ、どこ、どこ？ ちょっ、ぺこらさん！
Wait, where, where, where, where? Hey, Pekora-san!
ブンブンブン　ブンブンブン... インフルエンサー　ヘイヘイヘイ
Boom boom boom... Influencer, hey hey hey.
いつだって　知らないうちに
Always, before I knew it.
僕は見回している
I'm looking around.
何度も　君がどこで
Many times, where you are...
何をしているか　気になってしまうんだ
And what you're doing, I find myself wondering.
声くらい　かければいい
I should at least say something,
誰もが思うだろう
Anyone would think so.
できない　君がいる
I can't. If I knew...
場所がわかったら
Where you were,
僕には磁石になるんだ
You'd become a magnet for me.
気配以上　影は舞う
More than a presence, shadows dance.
恋はいつも　よそよそしい
Love is always distant.
胸騒ぎだ
My heart is fluttering.
超えられないように
So it cannot be overcome
世界から言葉なんか
If words and the like
消えてしまえばいい
Would just disappear from the world
地球と太陽みたいに
Like the Earth and the Sun
光と影が生まれて
Light and shadow are born
君を探してばかり
I'm always looking for you
距離は縮まらない
The distance never shortens
Hey! Hey! Hey! 引力 引力 惹かれて
Hey! Hey! Hey! Gravity, gravity, I'm drawn in
1から10まで君次第
From 1 to 10, it's all up to you
存在するだけで
Just by existing
影響与えてる
You're an influence
インフルエンサー
Influencer
人の噂 誰かなんて
Gossip about others, whoever they are
全然興味ないけど
I have absolutely no interest, but
なぜだか 君が何を考えてるか
For some reason, what you're thinking
知りたくてしょうがない
I can't help but want to know
Musicやファッションとか
Music, fashion, and such
映画や小説とか
Movies, novels, and such
何でもお気に入りのもの手にすれば
If I get my hands on any of your favorites
時間を共有できるんだ
Then we can share time together
外見よりも もっと深く
Deeper than outward appearances
恋は内面覗くことさ
Love is about looking inside
君に次第に 溺れてしまう
I'm gradually drowning in you
切なさが 物足りない
This heartache isn't enough
僕は叫んでいる
I'm screaming out
地球と太陽みたいに
Like the Earth and the Sun
意識と愛が回って
Consciousness and love revolve
君を思い続けよう
I'll keep thinking of you
宇宙の中心さ
You're the center of the universe
Hey! Hey! Hey! どんなに 離れて いたって
Hey! Hey! Hey! No matter how far apart we are
逆らいきれぬその力
That power cannot be resisted
もし君がいなくなったら
If you were to disappear
僕は僕じゃなくなる
I would no longer be myself
インフルエンサー
Influencer
地球と太陽みたいに
Like the Earth and the Sun
光と影が生まれて
Light and shadow are born
君を探してばかり
I'm always looking for you
距離は縮まらない
The distance never shortens
Hey! Hey! Hey! 引力 引力 惹かれて
Hey! Hey! Hey! Gravity, gravity, I'm drawn in
1から10まで君次第
From 1 to 10, it's all up to you
存在するだけで
Just by existing
影響与えてる
You're an influence
インフルエンサー
Influencer
ブンブンブン ブンブンブン
Boom boom boom, boom boom boom
インフルエンサー
Influencer
ブンブンブン ブンブンブン
Boom boom boom, boom boom boom
インフルエンサー
Influencer
二人ともホントにありがとー！
Thank you both so much!
ありがとー！ありがとー！
Thank you! Thank you!
久しぶり！久しぶり！二人ともありがとー！
It's been a while! It's been a while! Thank you both!
え、なんかめっちゃ久しぶりじゃない？
Wait, hasn't it been a really long time?
久しぶりです。
It's been a while.
久しぶりですね。
だってこの前はなんか、すごい脱獄しようぜ部屋からみたいなゲームやってきりな気がする。
I feel like the last time was when we played that game about escaping from a room or something.
何でこんな期間あいたの？え、何で？
Why was there such a long gap? Eh, why?
あー、はいはい、確かに確かに。
Ah, yeah, true, true.
なんかこの人なか、すごいなか、忘れてるよこれ、やばいよ。
This person is like, totally, she's forgotten. This is bad.
やばいよ。でもぺこちゃん的には遊びたいなって思ってるよ。
It's bad. But Pekora-chan does want to play together, I think.
本当に？なんか思ってなさそう。なさそうね。
Really? It doesn't seem like it. Doesn't seem so.
忘れてるよ。忘れてるよ。
She's forgotten. She's forgotten.
なんか寂しい。寂しいな。寂しい、なんか３人で仲良くやってたのに。
I'm kind of lonely. It's lonely. It's lonely, even though the three of us were getting along so well.
じゃあもうあれだよね。これ、ペボ、ペボになっちゃうね。
Then I guess that's it. It's becoming Pebo, Pebo.
ペボになっちゃうね。
It's becoming Pebo.
トトト！やばいやばい、ペボットでほらね、いろいろ、ほら。
To-to-to! Bad, bad, see, with Pebot, there's various... see.
本当に？
Really?
ほら！なんか３人でさ、なんか遊びたいペコだもんね。
See! It's because I want to play with the three of us, Peko.
そうだね。遊びたいね。またね、ぺこらもね、やりたいね。
That's right. I want to play. Again, I want to do it with Pekora too.
待ってます！
I'll be waiting!
ぺこら待ってます！
Pekora will be waiting!
二人とも本当にありがとね！
Thank you both so much!
またねー！バイバイ！バイバイ！
See you again! Bye bye! Bye bye!
バイバイー！
Bye bye!
あ、ぺこ、ぺこのどこ行こ...
Ah, where should Peko, Peko go...
帰り道は遠回りしたくなる
I want to take a detour on my way home
好きだった この場所
I loved this place
やめられない漫画を途中で閉じて
Closing the manga I couldn't stop reading halfway
顔を上げて気づくように
As if looking up and realizing
居心地いい日向もいつの間にか
The cozy sunny spot had turned into a shadow
影になってた そばを離れる
Before I knew it, I'm leaving its side
君と会って 過ぎる時間
Meeting you, the time passing
忘れるくらい 夢中で話した
I talked so intently I forgot everything
僕の夢は
My dream is
ここではない どこかへ
Somewhere other than here
帰り道は 帰り道は
On the way back, on the way back
遠回りを したくなるよ
I want to take the long way home
どこへ行けば どこに着くか
Where I'm going, where I'll arrive
過去の道なら 迷うことがないから
If it's the path of the past, I won't get lost
弱虫(弱虫)
Coward (Coward)
新しい世界へ
To a new world
今 行きたい(行きたい 行きたい 行きたい)
I want to go now (I want to go, I want to go...)
強くなりたい
I want to become strong
(Oh, oh, oh...) 好きだった この場所
(Oh, oh, oh...) I loved this place
(Oh, oh, oh...) 一歩目 踏み出そう
(Oh, oh, oh...) Let's take the first step
街明かりが寂しくふと感じるのは
Feeling the city lights lonely all of a sudden
見慣れた景色と違うから
Is because it's different from the scenery I know
いつもの歩道橋 見えなくなって
The usual pedestrian bridge is gone
どこにいるか わからない
I don't know where I am
人は誰も 変わることに 慣れていなくて
Everyone is not used to changing
昨日と同じように
Just like yesterday
今日も明日も ここにいたくなるんだ
Today and tomorrow too, I want to be here
知らない道 知らない道
Unknown paths, unknown paths
あと何回 歩けるだろう
How many more times can I walk them
夢のほうが 愛のほうが
Dreams or love
風は道を選んだりはしないよ
The wind doesn't choose its path
このまま(このまま)
Just like this (just like this)
ワンウェイの標識
A one-way sign
でも 行くんだ(行くんだ 行くんだ 行くんだ)
But I'm going (I'm going, I'm going...)
戻れなくても
Even if I can't go back
きっと離れるのは悲しいけど
Surely parting is sad, but
大事な別れだ
It's an important farewell
もっともっと 広い世界 知らなきゃいけない
I have to know a wider, wider world
いつか(いつか) きっと(きっと)
Someday (someday), surely (surely)
違う道を選んだ意味
The meaning of choosing different paths
輝く未来のためと 互いにわかるだろう
We'll both understand it's for a shining future
風のように 風のように
Like the wind, like the wind
思うままに 生きてみよう
Let's try to live as we please
過去がどんな 眩しくても
No matter how dazzling the past was
未来は もっと眩しいかもしれない
The future might be even more dazzling
帰り道は 帰り道は
On the way back, on the way back
遠回りを したくなるよ
I want to take the long way home
どこへ行けば どこに着くか
Where I'm going, where I'll arrive
過去の道なら 迷うことがないから
If it's the path of the past, I won't get lost
弱虫(弱虫)
Coward (Coward)
新しい世界へ
To a new world
今 行きたい(行きたい 行きたい 行きたい)
I want to go now (I want to go, I want to go...)
強くなりたい
I want to become strong
(Oh, oh, oh...) 好きだった この場所
(Oh, oh, oh...) I loved this place
(Oh, oh, oh...) 大切な思い出
(Oh, oh, oh...) Precious memories
(Oh, oh, oh...) 好きだった この場所
(Oh, oh, oh...) I loved this place
ぺこちゃん！
Peko-chan!
あずちゃん、３周年おめでとう！
AZ-chan, happy 3rd anniversary!
ありがとう、ぺこ！むしろ、来てくれてありがとう、ぺこ！
Thank you, peko! Rather, thank you for coming, peko!
こちらこそ、こんな素敵なライブに呼んでくれてありがとう！
Me too, thank you for inviting me to such a wonderful live!
嬉しい！嬉しい！
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
これは、約束の絆のあなぺこだよ、あずちゃん。
This is the promised bond of Ana-Peko, AZ-chan.
呼んでくれたきっかけ、何なんです？
What was the reason you invited me?
あ、待って待って待って！
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
でもぺこら、本当にあずちゃんと歌コラボをしたくて！
But Pekora really wanted to do a singing collab with AZ-chan!
嬉しい！まさか、受けてくれるなんて...。叶った叶った叶った！
I'm happy! I never thought you'd accept... It came true!
これからも誘ってもいいってことですか？
Does this mean I can invite you again?
もちろん！
Of course!
よっしゃ！
Yes!
二人で仲良く...
Let's get along, the two of us...
帰ろう！
Let's go home!
夏色
Natsuiro
君の家の猫はあくびをしながら
Your cat at home is yawning while
今日も一日を過ごしてゆく
it spends another day today.
何も変わらない
Nothing has changed in this
お馴染みのこの街並み
all too familiar cityscape.
みんな夏が来たって浮かれ気分なのに
Everyone's in a festive mood because summer has come,
君は一人冴えない顔してるね
but you're the only one with a dull look on your face.
そうだ君に見せたいものがあるんだ
That's right, there's something I want to show you.
大きな五時半の夕焼け
A big sunset at 5:30,
子どもの頃と同じように
just like when we were kids,
海も空も雲も 僕らでさえも 染めてゆくから
as it colors the sea, the sky, the clouds, and even us.
この長い長い下り坂を
Down this long, long downhill slope,
君を自転車の後ろに乗せて
with you on the back of my bicycle,
ブレーキいっぱい握りしめて
gripping the brakes tight,
ゆっくりゆっくり下ってゆく
we'll slowly, slowly go down.
A Perfect Sky
君の胸で泣かない
I won't cry in your arms.
君に胸貸さない
I won't lend you my shoulder.
I'm looking for a perfect sky
いたずらな猫みたく
Like a mischievous cat,
夏の陽をかすめて走る
running, brushing past the summer sun.
I'm looking for a perfect sky
HOT LIMIT
都会のビルの海じゃ
In the sea of urban buildings,
感じなくなってる君を
you've become numb.
いたわりの口づけで
With a caring kiss,
弱らせてとろかして
I'll weaken you and make you melt.
差し上げましょ！
Let me give it to you!
妖精たちが 夏を刺激する
The fairies stimulate summer,
生足 魅惑の マーメイド
mermaid with seductive bare legs.
出すとこ出して たわわになったら
Showing what's to be shown, when it's ripened,
宝物の君も オールオッケー
you, my treasure, are all okay too.
妖精 夏を 誰としたくなる
Fairy, who do you want to spend summer with?
一人寝の夜に You can say good-bye
You can say goodbye to nights sleeping alone.
奥の方まで 乾かないままで
Until the deep inside, without drying out,
本気の夏恋しなせえな
let's have a serious summer love.
secret base ～君がくれたもの～
secret base ~Kimi ga Kureta Mono~
君と夏の終わり 将来の夢
The end of summer with you, dreams of the future,
大きな希望 忘れない
and big hopes, I won't forget them.
10年後の8月
In August, ten years from now,
また出会えるのを 信じて
I believe we'll meet again.
最高の 思い出を…
The best memories...
出会いはふとした瞬間
Our meeting was just a sudden moment,
帰り道の交差点で
at the intersection on the way home.
声をかけてくれたね
You called out to me,
「一緒に帰ろう」
saying, 'Let's go home together.'
僕は照れくさそうにカバンで顔を隠しながら
Blushing, I hid my face behind my bag...
本当はとてもとても嬉しかったよ
...but the truth is, I was very, very happy.
あぁ 花火が夜空 綺麗に咲いて ちょっとせつなく
Ah, fireworks bloom beautifully in the night sky,
feeling a bit bittersweet.
あぁ 風が時間とともに流れる
Ah, the wind flows along with time.
嬉しくて 楽しくて 冒険もいろいろしたね
We were happy, having fun,
and went on all sorts of adventures.
二人の秘密の基地の中
Inside our secret base.
君と夏の終わり 将来の夢 大きな希望 忘れない
I won't forget that end of summer with you,
our dreams for the future, and our great hopes.
10年後の8月 また出会えるのを 信じて
Believing that we'll meet again in August,
ten years from now.
君が最後まで心から 「ありがとう」叫んでいたこと 知ってたよ
I knew that you were shouting "thank you"
from the bottom of your heart until the very end.
涙をこらえて 笑顔でさよなら せつないよね
Holding back tears and saying goodbye with a smile
is painful, isn't it?
最高の思い出を...
To the best of memories...
あぁ 夏休みもあと少しで終わっちゃうから
Ah, because summer vacation is almost over...
あぁ 太陽と月 仲良くして
Ah, let the sun and moon get along.
悲しくて 寂しくて 喧嘩もいろいろしたね
We were sad, feeling lonely,
and had all sorts of fights.
二人の秘密の基地の中
Inside our secret base.
君が最後まで心から 「ありがとう」叫んでいたこと 知ってたよ
I knew that you were shouting "thank you"
from the bottom of your heart until the very end.
涙をこらえて 笑顔でさよなら せつないよね
Holding back tears and saying goodbye with a smile
is painful, isn't it?
最高の思い出を...
To the best of memories...
突然の...
Suddenly...
転校で...
you transferred schools...
どうしようもなく
and there was nothing I could do.
手紙書くよ 電話もするよ
I'll write letters, I'll call you.
忘れないでね 僕のことを
Don't forget me.
いつまでも二人の基地の中
Always inside our base.
君と夏の終わり ずっと話して 夕日を見てから星を眺め
At the end of summer with you, we talked forever,
watched the sunset, and then gazed at the stars.
君の頬を流れた涙はずっと忘れない
I'll never forget the tears
that flowed down your cheeks.
君が最後まで大きく手を振ってくれたこと きっと忘れない
I'll surely never forget how you waved your hand
so wide until the very end.
だからこうして夢の中で ずっと永遠に...
So, just like this, inside a dream,
forever and ever...
君と夏の終わり 将来の夢 大きな希望 忘れない
I won't forget that end of summer with you,
our dreams for the future, and our great hopes.
10年後の8月 また出会えるのを 信じて
Believing that we'll meet again in August,
ten years from now.
君が最後まで心から 「ありがとう」叫んでいたこと 知ってたよ
I knew that you were shouting "thank you"
from the bottom of your heart until the very end.
涙をこらえて 笑顔でさよなら せつないよね
Holding back tears and saying goodbye with a smile
is painful, isn't it?
最高の思い出を...
To the best of memories...
(歓声)
(Cheering)
なんだこの空気は
What's with this atmosphere?
この空気は...
This atmosphere...
ぺこら ぺこらちゃん 3周年おめでとう！
Pekora, Pekora-chan... Congrats on your 3rd anniversary!
いや みんな来てくれて本当にありがとう イェーイ！
No, thank you everyone so much for coming! Yay!
いや 夏メロメドレー めちゃくちゃ斬新で良かった！
Man, that nostalgic summer medley was so fresh and great!
みんなでね それぞれなんか歌いたい曲とか
Everyone chose songs they wanted to sing...
でもね ぺこら シークレットベースもすごかったんだけど め組の人！
But you know, Pekora, "Secret Base" was great,
but "Megumi no Hito"!
め組のぺこらだよ
It's Megumi no Pekora!
楽しかったね。ね、旦那様もみんなでさ
It was fun. Right, Danna-sama and everyone?
久しぶりに歌えて本当に良かった ぺこら。
It was great singing together again after so long, Pekora.
なんか3周年 エモいね。
3rd anniversary... it's emotional.
エモエモだね。これからもよろしくお願いします。
Very emotional. Please continue to support me.
お願いします。じゃあもうぺこら 配信終わりっすか？
Please do. So, Pekora, is the stream ending now?
あ 違う 違う まだ。この後にもうちょびっとだけあるぺこら。
Oh, no, no, not yet! There's a little bit more after this, peko.
え、何があるの？秘密？
Eh, what is it? A secret?
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
あれ？これ何ぺこ？
Wait? What is this, Peko?
やっぱりこれだよねー
As expected, it's this.
何かな？
I wonder what it is?
なんかあるのかな？他に。
Is there something else?
あるかもしれないぺこだから！
Because there might be, Peko!
じゃあ皆、お別れできないよ！
Wait, we can't say goodbye yet!
できないよー！
We can't!
見て見て！
Look, look!
楽しみ！
I'm excited!
帰れないよ！
We can't go home!
じゃあまた皆遊ぼうぺこな！
Alright, let's all play again, Peko!
またねー！
See you!
バイバーイ！
Bye bye!
落ちるか？
Are you gonna fall?
落ちろ！落ちろ！
Fall! Fall!
キャー！
Aaaah!
てなわけで、告知タイムいこうと思うぺこー！
So, I'm going to start the announcement time, Peko!
はい、そしたらなら、今日は告知が二つあります！
Okay, so today I have two announcements!
皆、聞く準備はできてるぺこですか？
Everyone, are you ready to listen, Peko?
じゃあ早速、多分もう待てないと思うぺこだか告知させてもらうぺこ！
Then, without further ado, since I think you can't wait, let me make the announcements, Peko!
一つ目はこちら！ドーン！
The first one is this! Boom!
活動3周年記念グッズ 7月17日 販売開始
3rd Anniversary Memorial Goods. Sales start July 17th.
兎田ぺこら三周年記念グッズが発売になるぺこー！イエーイ！
Usada Pekora's 3rd anniversary memorial goods will be released! Yay!
まあ見てわかると思うぺこだけど、今回のグッズはテーマ、「冒険」。
Well, I think you can tell by looking, but the theme for this time's goods is "Adventure".
まあ「勇者」？
Well, "Hero"?
そんな感じになってるぺこだけど、なんでこんな感じになってるかはあとの次の告知でわかるぺこだから、ちょっと考えてみてぺこな！
It's like that, but you'll find out why in the next announcement, so please think about it, Peko!
そしたらなら、グッズの紹介をしていこうと思うぺこ！
So, I'm going to introduce the goods, Peko!
まず一つ目は、タペストリー！これ黒鉄屋先生にね、描いていただきました！
First is the tapestry! This was drawn by Kurogane-ya-sensei!
そして、ぺこらと野うさぎのドットラバーキーホルダー！
And the Pekora and Nousagi dot rubber keyholders!
ロングタオル！
Long towel!
ポーチの四つになってるぺこ！
And the pouch, so there are four in total, Peko!
こちらね、あのフルセットを買っていただいた方限定で、
For those who buy the full set,
黒鉄屋先生描き下ろしのポストカードがついてくるぺこなのぜ是非是非皆さん、お手に取っていただきたいと思うぺこ！
it comes with a postcard drawn by Kurogane-ya-sensei, so I really hope everyone gets one, Peko!
そして、二つ目の告知になっちゃうぺこですけども、
And now for the second announcement, Peko,
まあわかったよね？多分ね、もうわかってるぺこだよね？
well, you know it, right? You probably already know it, right?
さあ、こちら！ドーン！
Well, here it is! Boom!
兎田ぺこら 3rd Original Song ララララビット！！
Usada Pekora 3rd Original Song 'LALALA RABBIT!!'
兎田ぺこら三曲目のオリソン、「ララララビット！！」が発売になるぺこー！イエーイ！
Usada Pekora's 3rd original song, 'LALALA RABBIT!!', will be released! Yay!
本日の24時からリリースとなっていますぺこですので、たくさん聴いてくれると嬉しいぺこです！
It will be released today at midnight, so I'd be happy if you listen to it a lot, Peko!
なんと作詞作曲、ナユタン星人さんなんです！ありがとうございます！
Actually, the lyrics and composition are by Nayutan Seijin-san! Thank you very much!
え？何？早く聴けないかって？
Huh? What? "Can't we hear it sooner?"
ああ、そんなわがままな子もいるぺこなと思ったから...
Ah, I thought there might be some selfish children like that, Peko...
聴けちゃいます！なんとこのあと、オリソンを歌うぺこなので、お楽しみに！
You can! Actually, I'm going to sing the original song after this, so please look forward to it!
てなわけで、準備してくるぺこね！バイバイ！
So, I'm going to go get ready, Peko! Bye bye!
旅立とう 冒険 そしてインドアの神話へ
Let's set out on an adventure, to the indoor mythology
最大級の ララララビット！！
The greatest, LALALA RABBIT!!
最弱盤のスライムにビビるのが大概なマイライフ
My life is mostly about being scared of the weakest slime
ワン・トゥ・スリーで繋がったセカイに愛あふれだす
Love overflows in the world connected by one, two, three
8-bitに感じるドキドキ
A heart-pounding 8-bit feeling
2Dのラブじゃダメですか？
Is a 2D love not enough?
運ゲー状態 ふざけんじゃないぞ
It's a luck-based game, don't mess around
レベルアップして超えてやらぁ！
I'll level up and overcome it!
夢に見てるファンファーレの音
The sound of the fanfare I've dreamed of
乱数調整 一件攻勢 一点突破 想定外も
RNG manipulation, a sudden offensive, a breakthrough, even the unexpected
ロマンスの過程
A process of romance
ラヴィラヴィ ちいさなビットにでっかいアイを交信中
Lovey-lovey, transmitting a big love in small bits
ちょっと沼っても許してね？
Forgive me if I get a bit obsessed?
いつだって愛は非効率！
Love is always inefficient!
jumpin' jumpin' 跳ねるハートを捕まえて おいでね！
Jumpin' jumpin', catch this bouncing heart and come here!
二兎なんて追わないで
Don't try to chase two rabbits
トゥルーエンドになるまで
Until we reach the true ending
最大級の ララララビット！！
The greatest, LALALA RABBIT!!
人生とかけて無理ゲーと説く どちらもクリアがみえません！
Betting my life and calling it an impossible game, I can't see the clear for either!
このラブって状態異常を解く アイテムはどこで買えますか！？
Where can I buy an item to cure this "love" status ailment!?
攻略も説明も足りないクソゲー！！
A shitty game with no walkthrough or explanation!!
いや、足りないのわたしのINT！？
No, is it my INT that's lacking!?
まあ、どんな難所も超えてやるけど
Well, I'll overcome any difficult spot though
そのまえに誰かいいものありますか？
Before that, does anyone have something good?
ちゃんと届いてる あなたのエール
Your cheers are reaching me clearly
一進一退 八方塞がり 絶体絶命 大失敗も
One step forward, one step back, boxed in on all sides, a desperate situation, even a big failure
サクセスの序章
The prologue to success
ラヴィラヴィ ちいさなビットででっかいセカイ交信中
Lovey-lovey, transmitting a big world with small bits
うまくいかないプレイング
Poor playing
迷走だって あなたとしたい
I want to stray with you.
わたしを見ててほしいの よそ見はしないでね
I want you to look at me, don't look away, okay?
不器用でも愛してね
Love me even if I'm clumsy
もっと跳べるから
Because I can jump even more
ラヴィ ラヴィ まだまだあなたと でっかいアイを更新中！
Lavi, Lavi, still updating a huge love with you!
暴走しちゃったら制してね？
If I go out of control, please stop me, okay?
だって愛は非常識！
Because love is irrational!
ラヴィ もっともっと跳ねてたいから
Lavi, I want to keep bouncing more and more
ずっとそばで見ていてね！
So please watch me from by my side forever!
どんな想いでもくださいな
Please give me any kind of feelings
月まで届くくらいに
Enough to reach the moon
最大級のララララヴィ
The greatest La-la-la-Lavi
(ラビット！)
(Rabbit!)
もっとしたいの！ ララララヴィ
I want to do it more! La-la-la-Lavi
(ラビット！)
(Rabbit!)
みんなー！3周年ライブどうぺこだったー？
Everyone! How was the 3rd anniversary live, peko?
うー、わー！
Ooh, wah!
このあと10時15分から
Starting from 10:15 PM after this
メンバー限定のアフターライブもあるので、ぜひぜひ見に来てね！
There will be a members-only after-live, so please come and watch!
4年目もぺこらストーリー歩もうぜ！
Let's walk the Pekora story in the 4th year too!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!